<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>E-commerce Microservices on AWS on AWS System Manager</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in E-commerce Microservices on AWS on AWS System Manager</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/cdk-setup-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cdk-setup-guide/</guid>
      <description>E-commerce Microservices CDK Setup Guide Quick Start This guide will help you set up the CDK infrastructure for our e-commerce microservices workshop.
Prerequisites  AWS CLI configured with appropriate permissions Node.js (v16 or later) AWS CDK installed globally Docker for building container images  Installation Steps 1. Install AWS CDK npm install -g aws-cdk 2. Verify Installation cdk --version 3. Bootstrap CDK (First time only) cdk bootstrap aws://ACCOUNT-NUMBER/REGION Project Structure ecommerce-microservices-cdk/├── bin/│ └── app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/productservice-implementation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/productservice-implementation/</guid>
      <description>Product Service Implementation Overview The Product Service is responsible for managing the product catalog in our e-commerce microservices architecture. It handles product information, categories, pricing, and metadata.
API Endpoints GET /api/v1/products List all products with pagination and filtering capabilities.
Query Parameters:
 page (optional): Page number (default: 1) limit (optional): Items per page (default: 20, max: 100) category (optional): Filter by category search (optional): Search term for product names/descriptions minPrice (optional): Minimum price filter maxPrice (optional): Maximum price filter  Response:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
